[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Julio] He's really getting on my nerves.
Teach that bastard, Diego, a lesson.
If you're reading this,
it means you got lucky.
But I'll make sure
you won't be as lucky next time.
[Jerry] I just want to talk to the mayor.
He needs to know what I know.
You have to trust me.
I'm sure you won't regret it.
[Camia] I didn't get any information
here at the city hall.
But I'm sure the Ardientes
are hiding something
in the group Emilia established.
[Ivy] Mom, Emilia just told me
something that matches up
with the information you're getting.
[Arnaldo] What am I
supposed to do with this thing?
-Smash it on your head?
-Mayor.
Mayor, first ask what exactly
is in that cellphone.
This contains the dark truth
about your beloved Ivy.
[Raul] About your campaign for later.
I don't think you should go.
Julio's planning something
against you and it's not good.
He's going to kill you, son.
I can take care of myself, Dad.
[Ivy] Arnaldo, you monster.
I'll kill you before
you find out who I really am.
[Arnaldo] I'll make you pay
for lying to me, Ivy Aguas.
Proceed with the plan.
Understood, sir.
[ominous music playing]
[inaudible] Boss.
For now, the coast is clear,
so we're good.
Boss, what are we doing here
at a nursing home?
Like I said, we're here
to watch over Diego
and his campaign.
To support him.
All right.
Mr. Jaguar, the coast is clear.
Boss.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Camia] Hello, there!
-Please have some sandwiches.
-Hello!
Talk to Auntie.
Oh, it's still hot!
[Camia] There's more where that came from!
[Camia] Help yourselves.
Congratulations, Governor Diego!
You're the winner to me.
It's a good thing you didn't
cancel your campaign here.
These people are so happy to see you here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
-[line busy]
-Diego.
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello? Who is this?
My lovely brother.
Arnaldo.
[line busy]
How are you today?
Well, I'm sorry to bother you.
It's just that…
I was thinking about our childhood.
We never really got close,
and I wonder why?
But then, I realized it.
I was never a good brother to you.
And I apologize, okay? I apologize.
[Arnaldo] I regretted it because somehow
I thought, we could've been close.
We could've bonded like best friends.
Why are you telling me this now?
Well, the reason why I'm telling you this
is because I'm jealous!
So jealous! I'm jealous…
of your close friendship… with this…
[clicking fingers]
What's her name? Lily Cruz.
Your best friend?
What do you want from Lily?
[Diego] I'm warning you,
if you do anything to hurt her,
you'll have to deal with me.
See?! Here you are with the threats!
Never-ending threats.
I just said I was jealous of
your friendship with Lily Cruz!
Now, here you are,
picking a fight with me.
You're blaming me again.
Here I am, trying to confess my feelings,
and then there you are.
Trying to rub it in my face. I'm hurt.
Okay?
And besides, I'm not talking about
the Lily Cruz that you're with.
Okay? She's an impostor.
[suspenseful music playing]
That's right.
That is the wrong Lily Cruz.
And I'm with the right one.
Ding! Ding! Ding! We have a winner!
But somehow…
I feel… that you already know that.
I'm going to make her regret all
the things that she did to me.
-And then, I'll kill her.
-Arnaldo…
I will kill your Lily Cruz, Diego!
[stuttering] Arnaldo, please?
And then, I'll let you know.
And then, maybe we can be best
friends? Start from scratch.
Anyway, I have to go.
I have to kill someone.
[suspenseful music playing]
[exhales sharply]
Such a lovely day today!
It's a good day to kill someone.
Diego, is something wrong?
Ivy's life is in danger.
Diego, wait!
I said wait, Diego!
[panting]
Wait, Diego. What happened to Lily?
Arnaldo knows the truth.
He knows she's Lily Cruz.
I have to go save her!
Don't worry. I'll save Ivy.
Just be careful, okay?
I will.
There's a bomb! There's a bomb!
There's a bomb, everyone! Look out!
-What?!
-Mr. Diego.
-Where?
-There's a bomb!
It's with the donation packages,
Governor! It's going to explode!
Go find Lily!
-We'll take care of this.
-It's going to explode!
No, wait. I have to make sure
everyone's safe first.
-It's going to explode!
-A-all right. Calm down, please.
Everyone, please calm down!
Let's all calm down, please.
Don't panic. We'll call for backup.
[Diego] All right, let's get them
out of here.
Batch, call the bomb squad.
-All right.
-Hurry! I'll be right back.
Okay. Okay.
[Diego] Michael, keep everyone
calm. Let's not panic, everyone.
[suspenseful music playing]
You guys take care of this, okay?
Okay.
[crowd sobbing]
Stay calm, everyone. Help is on the way.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Ivy?
Mom. Mom, we have a problem.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hon.
Ivy…
there's a bomb threat
at Diego's campaign site!
The bomb's inside,
so we can't be sure we're safe!
Let's go?
I'll just call you later, okay?
Let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
[music intensifies]
[inaudible] Let's go, Hon.
Anna, stand back.
Wait. Stand back!
[bomb ticking]
Diego, it is a bomb!
Let's get out of here!
It's dangerous!
Come on! We have to run away!
Where's the bomb squad?
What's taking them so long?!
-There's a bomb!
-A bomb?!
There's a bomb?! Anna.
Let's go.
Boss, I'll get Diego.
-Be careful, okay?
-Evacuate everyone!
Emilia's "good jobs" are child's play.
I, Julio Ardiente…
[Julio] will give this town the
biggest scare of their lives!
Please move faster!
Make way for the elderly!
-Where are Diego and Anna?!
-They went to the second floor!
Why on earth did they go there?!
What if the bomb explodes?! Pandoy!
-Where's Camia?!
-Sir, please keep moving!
Sir, they're on the second floor. Hurry!
-Pandoy!
-Okay, here.
[screaming]
[Camia] Go ahead!
[heavy breathing]
Oh my!
Sir, ma'am, just calm down. Let's go.
We need to get out of here.
Let's go.
-Anna?!
-Jepoy, over here!
The bomb's here!
-What's that?
-Stand back!
[bomb ticking]
[laughs mockingly]
Is there anything we can do to help?
Just stand back, sir. Leave this to us.
-All right.
-It's a vintage bomb.
It won't be easy to detonate.
That's right. It's a bomb.
A bomb that can take your lives out!
It's a bomb that's gonna scare
the wits out of your brains!
[Julio] It's a big bomb!
-Why isn't it stopping?
-Cut the black cord!
[Julio] Go ahead. Turn pale!
Get scared! Because that bomb…
[suspenseful music playing]
[bomb continues ticking]
…is nothing! [laughs]
It's confirmed. This bomb is fake.
That is a vintage World War I bomb!
It's gonna take another bomb
to blow it up!
It won't go off!
But it will surely scare
the daylights out of you! [laughs]
It was just planted here to scare you.
Bunch of brainless maggots!
They were easily terrified!
What more if I actually kill
them and blow up their bodies?
[scoffs]
Col. Sanggano, you know what to do.
Yes, sir.
Emilia? What are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be at
the rest house with my grandson?
I've been there, Papa.
Arnaldo is doing fine.
I'm just here to attend to some matters.
Oh.
Covering your tracks?
[laughs]
Someone is investigating
your little committee.
They're trying to find out how
you stole funds worth millions.
Your past is coming after you, Emilia.
And if they get to the bottom
of your case…
you'll never get away with it.
Not now, not ever.
Papa, even without your support,
I have people around me
who will support my candidacy.
Oh?
So you have people behind you
who will support your candidacy.
I assume one of them is… Ivy Aguas.
You know, you're such a gullible woman.
Really now, Papa? Me, gullible?
Weren't you the one
who was so impressed with her?
Of course, I said that
to give her the illusion that I trust her!
Emilia, how many times do I have to… argh!
Remember this: I wouldn't be
surprised if I find out
that Ms. Aguas is behind
the investigations against you!
Shush!
[ominous music playing]
Do you want some wine?
Yes, please.
Okay. Feel free.
We're the only ones here,
so you can do whatever you want.
I can do whatever I want.
[suspenseful music playing]
Here you go.
Thank you.
Cheers.
[glasses clink]
I can't wait for you to fully recover.
I wish you'd get better soon.
I appreciate that.
I love you.
I really, really love you, Ivy.
You know what? I have a better idea.
Just to keep things interesting and fun…
I brought some toys.
[chuckles]
-Arnaldo.
-Come on. Just humor me.
This will be fun.
Your hands, please.
Both hands.
Do you want me to be your slave?
Yeah, I'd like--
Why don't we… do it the other way around?
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
You know what?
Have you ever danced with the devil?
[laughs softly]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
Put down your gun, Ivy.
I'm not playing games anymore.
I'm not playing either, Arnaldo.
[guns clicking]
If that's what you want.
[grunts]
-Is this what you wanted?
-I wanted this, but…
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[chuckling]
Go on. Is this what you really want?
Pull the trigger! Pull the trigger.
You can't do it?
-Don't try to scare me.
-You can't do it
because I'm still part
of your plans against my family.
So, if you won't pull the trigger, I will!
[both grunt]
That's it?
[sighs]
You're out already?!
I'm just getting started.
[ominous music playing]
Emilia, what's happening?
Tell me everything, I'll understand.
No, Auntie. You don't need
to know anything, okay?
And besides, you won't be able to help.
Please, leave me alone.
[line ringing]
Hello, Jaguar?
Jaguar, you're the only one I can trust.
Papa is making me paranoid again
and I can't trust Ivy Aguas.
Please, I need your help.
I need to talk to you.
I need to see you.
[tense music playing]
Oh, thank goodness!
Don't worry, the bomb was fake.
They tried to scare us.
-Thank goodness!
-Mr. Diego, can you come
with us to the precinct
so we can get a statement?
-We can handle things here.
-You got this, Batch?
-Okay.
-Anna, I need to go.
-Thank you so much.
-Aunt Camia, I need to go.
Wait, is there a problem?
What's wrong?
Arnaldo knows that Ivy
is the real Lily Cruz.
-What?!
-Yes, Auntie.
Lily's life is in danger.
Then I'm coming with you, Diego.
I promise I'll bring back
Ivy safe and sound.
-Diego, go.
-Don't worry. Don't you worry.
-Diego.
-Anna, I'll be off.
Diego, I'll come with you. Come on.
Take care, okay?
[Diego] Be careful.
Auntie Camia.
[suspenseful music playing]
Well, rise and shine! How was your sleep?
Arnaldo, what is this?
What is this? Why am I tied up?
What are you doing to me?
I love you and take care of you
and you act like you want to kill me?
-Oh wow.
-Take these off!
Look at you!
You're such a good actress.
I'm so blown away.
So captivating, so emotional?
-Take these off!
-Oh my… Ladies and gentlemen!
And the best actress award
goes to… Lily Cruz!
In her most daring role as Ivy Aguas.
Arnaldo, what are you talking about?
What are you saying?
Can you just release me?
Hon!
I'm taking care of you
because I want you to get well
so we can get married, remember?
[chuckling] You're taking
care of me? But I will kill you!
Because I killed for you!
Okay? I've done so much for you.
I killed so many people…
-Arnal--
-…for you. Nimfa. Jerry.
Mayor, before anything else,
can you help me out first?
One million. That's nothing.
Ten million, Mayor.
That's nothing to you, Mayor.
Come on, Mayor.
Mayor.
[grunts]
I almost killed my own mother
because of you.
So… look at me. Look at me.
I deserve the right to know the truth.
-Arnaldo!
-I want to hear it
straight from your mouth.
Lily Cruz. Lily Cruz. Tell me.
You're Lily Cruz, right?
Tell me. Tell me.
[grunts]
So, Lily Cruz, tell me.
You are Lily Cruz, right?
-I am not Lily.
-Liar!
Liar.
I have proof. I have proof.
Listen. Watch this.
And I have no proof
because you deleted it.
I'm going to kill you!
[grunts]
Arnaldo!
You're insane!
The fight in you.
I've always loved that about you.
Arnaldo, what are you doing?
I am not Lily Cruz.
Tell me the truth…
-I am telling the truth.
-or I'll kill you.
[gunshot]
The next one will go straight
to your brain.
Now, tell me the truth. Answer me!
[tense music playing]
Yes!
I am! I am Lily Cruz!
I am Lily Cruz!
I am Lily Cruz! You're right!
Hi, Mr. Mayor. Yes.
Oh yes, Mr. Mayor. I am… Lily Cruz.
Didn't you hear me? I'm Lily Cruz!
-[angry shouts]
-[gun firing]
I used you. Just so you know, I used you!
I never really loved you.
I've always hated you.
Everything between us was a lie.
I'd never fall in love with a criminal!
I'd never fall for an Ardiente!
Congressman, Diego Torillo's
no longer in the vicinity.
Predictable. Well now, let's activate
the next level of our obstacle course.
Have someone follow him.
[Julio] And don't come back
to me until you're ready to
serve me that bastard's head on a plate.
Diego, where are we going to look for Ivy?
At the Ardientes' old rest house.
That's where they took her.
We have to hurry.
-Diego, we're being followed!
-What?
We're being followed!
It's Julio Ardiente's men!
-Step on it! Hurry!
-[engine revving]
[guns firing]
[tire screeching]
-[Jepoy] I'm out of bullets!
-Get out of there!
[Diego] Wait.
Stubborn, eh?
-Wait, wait!
-You're so stubborn!
-We don't want to fight.
-Finish them.
Let's finish this.
Wait, we don't want to fight.
Jepoy, you know what to do.
Let's go.
[men grunting]
[gun fires]
Diego.
-Try me!
-Nobody move!
All right, get in! Hurry!
Just try and move…
-Let's go, Jepoy!
-…and I'll blow your brains out!
Don't!
[tense music playing]
Get up! Let's go! After them!
You know what you did wrong?
You were born an Ardiente.
All because you're Raul and Emilia's son!
Do you know what your father did?
Your damned father destroyed my family!
Your mother had my father killed
and my mother raped
all because she was jealous!
And, you?
I started with you because you
were the weakest of them all.
[scoffs]
And now, you just had to give me
another reason to hate you.
Do you know why I'm driving you crazy?
Well? Because you killed Nanny Carlotta!
You killed her! You monster!
You're crazy! You're a criminal!
Well, I guess that makes us even.
We're even now.
Because you made a fool out of me.
You lied to me.
You made me look like an idiot.
And for that, I'm going to kill you!
I'm going to kill you! Did you hear that?
I will kill you.
But, not yet.
See? Not yet.
No easy way out for you, Hon.
Your death isn't enough to make
up for everything you've done
to make a fool out of me and my family.
[laughs]
That's exactly what I'd tell myself
while I was plotting how to take you down.
And that's why you're still alive.
Except for your screwed-up
mind and soul, that is.
Have you heard anything from Diego?
Not yet, Mr. Pandoy.
I hope both he and Jepoy
manage to save Ivy.
-Camia.
-Uncle, Auntie.
-Auntie.
-What is it?
I've called the police
and they're on their way
to the rest house.
[tense music playing]
[Diego] Ivy! Ivy! Ivy! Anything, Jepoy?
-They're not downstairs.
-Check that room over there!
-Ivy!
-Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
Ivy!
-Diego…
-Ivy! Well?
There's no one else here.
Where are you, Ivy?
-They might be at the yacht.
-Yacht?
Yeah, come on! Hurry!
[sighs]
You know what? I've always imagined
what it would be like had
our wedding pushed through.
What our honeymoon could have been?
Would it have been full of love? Passion?
Was it going to be romantic,
or full of lust?
But then again, what's stopping me now
from making that fantasy a reality?
-You bastard.
-Nothing.
-Nothing. Look at you!
Helpless. Hon?
-You and your father are so damn alike.
-Oh, yes.
You're just as sick as him, Arnaldo.
Yes! Like you said, I'm an Ardiente!
And I'm going to act like one!
I'm going to make you mine!
[grunts]
No! You're mine!
[screams]
You bastard! Arnaldo!
[young Lily] Get away from me,
please! I said, let go!
Mom!
You monster!
Stop it! This is the only thing
that's keeping you alive!
Arnaldo! You bastard!
Arnaldo!
You bastard!
Diego!
[grunts]
Ivy…
[suspenseful music playing]
Diego.
[grunts]
Arnaldo!
Stop it!
Diego…
Diego!
Come here.
Diego.
-Put the gun down, Arnaldo!
-No!
-I said, put it down!
I'm going to blow her brains out.
You love her, right?
-Arnaldo…
-You love her, right?!
Put the gun down.
I'll blow her brains out, you hear me?
Put the gun down!
You can't have her!
I'm going to blow her brains out!
If I can't have her, you can't either.
I'm just being fair, dear brother!
-Arnaldo.
-No.
-Arnaldo, don't.
-Arnaldo.
-No!
-Arnaldo!
No!
-[gunshot]
-[Ivy screams]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Jepoy!
-Ivy.
Are you all right?
[Diego] Hurry up, Jepoy!
Is Arnaldo dead?
-Let's go!
-Let's go! Come on!
Come on!
-Come on!
-Wait!
[Diego] Wait! Wait!
Let's go! Come on!
Arnaldo.
There's a pulse.
Let's take him to the hospital.
-Move! I'm going to kill him!
-Stop!
Wait, he's my brother!
Don't kill him.
We aren't murderers, Jepoy.
-Ivy.
-Jepoy, go on.
Get out of here, you two.
I'll take care of this.
I'll bring him to the hospital.
No. We're not leaving you.
[police siren blaring]
Just go!
If the police find you two,
the Ardientes are going to kill us.
Ivy, we can't let you face
the Ardientes by yourself.
Diego, please. I can handle myself.
Ivy, I shot him.
I should pay for this, not you.
Ivy, Arnaldo knows that you're Lily.
If we leave you?
Listen to me, both of you!
The police are here!
Diego, Jepoy, you are my allies
outside the Ardientes.
While I'm working at them from within.
So please, don't ruin the plan.
The police are here!
-Ivy.
-He's going to--
We're not leaving you! We're not--
Listen to me! You two should leave!
-That's enough, Ivy.
-He's still alive! I can take care of him!
-Jepoy, listen. Ivy's right.
-Jepoy, go!
Ivy, call us before the night is over.
-All right, I will.
-If you don't…
we'll attack the Ardientes ourselves.
-Are you nuts?!
-Come on!
-Jepoy, let's go!
-Ivy, call us!
[police siren blaring]
Congressman…
Diego and Jepoy escaped.
They're like rats
running away scared. Cowards.
Well, I don't have time to waste on them.
Colonel, send some of your men
to the rest house.
I can't seem to get in touch
with Ivy and Arnaldo.
I just want to make sure
that they're safe.
Yes, sir.
-[tense music playing]
-[police siren blaring]
Arnaldo! Help! Help us! Arnaldo!
-Don't move!
-Officer! Please help Arnaldo.
Please call an ambulance.
-Call an ambulance.
-Hurry!
-Hurry up!
-Are you deaf?!
Call an ambulance!
Arnaldo, no! No, no, no, please!
[sobbing]
Jaguar?
[sighs]
He's late again.
[door closes]
[slow tense music playing]
Jaguar.
I thought you weren't coming.
Let's not stay here.
Okay.
You can take me anywhere
you want. Anywhere in the world.
[Diego] Ivy, if I don't hear from you,
I'll tear the Ardientes apart.
Ivy can't know that I know
she's having me investigated.
Thank you.
What do you want me to say?
What do I have to do?
Well…
thank you for helping me,
Jaguar, and for listening.
I want to repay you.
But why? I want to see your face.
I don't understand. I want to
touch you. I want to see you.
Emilia?
Why don't you talk
to your husband about this?
[sighs]
Are we going to talk about Raul again?
I can't believe that
it's always been Raul.
And this is the only chance that we get
when we're together,
and you want us to talk about Raul?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't love him anymore.
No matter how hard he tries,
I don't want him.
I don't love him anymore.
I regret the day I married him.
I want you, Jaguar.
I want to marry you. Please.
No.
Huh?
I'm… I'm speech-- I don't understand.
You can't leave him.
You can't worsen the situation
you have at home.
You need to stay there
so we know Julio Ardiente's every move.
That's the only way
we can take everything from him.
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
What game are you playing, Emilia?
I'm taking everything back.
-So, where have you been?
-I met up with Jaguar, Auntie.
So that's why you have that aura.
Well, you know, Auntie,
I feel like I'm committing
a crime every time I meet with Jaguar.
Well, can you still call that a crime
when you've cut all ties
with your husband?
You and Raul are over so you're
free to do whatever you want.
Well, yeah, exactly, Auntie.
But you know? I'm just thinking…
earlier, Jaguar told me
to get back together with Raul
so that he can carry out his plan.
What do you think his plan is, Auntie?
You know, Jaguar is like
a puzzle… that I can't solve.
-Let's go, Aunt Claire.
-Emilia.
Hold on. Where were you? Why
do you look like that?
Mamita.
I met up with a friend of mine.
You dressed up like that
to meet up with a friend?
Why, Raul? I'm always dressed
up like this, even at home?
Emilia, be honest with me.
Tell me the truth.
Where were you?
Why are you dressed like that?
Why are you so worked up?!
For all I care, you shouldn't
have a say on wherever I go
because we're done! What's up with you?!
Emilia, may I just remind you
that our separation isn't official yet.
No matter what you say,
no matter how you look at it,
we're still married.
I still have the right
to know where you are
and what you're doing.
What if I told you
that I met up with Jaguar?
Well?
Why are you…? Why is Jaguar…?
Why do you always drag Jaguar into this?!
Are you trying to make me jealous?!
Emilia, I'm not jealous.
That won't work on me.
Just stop it, please!
-You're not jealous?
-No!
Then why are you angry?!
Emilia, can you stop seeing that Jaguar?
That Jaguar deserves
to have bullets in his guts.
What if he put bullets in yours?!
Why are you acting like this, Raul?
Are you proud of yourself
because Natalie likes you?
Don't think so highly of yourself!
Because for your information,
she screws anyone who looks her way.
So get off your high horse!
You're just acting like this
because someone else
is taking interest in me!
So quit it.
Emilia, wait?
Emilia!
Congressman? Congressman…
-Colonel, what's the update?
-Sir…
We've finally gotten ahold of Ivy Aguas.
-And?
-Something happened to the mayor.
What?
He's in critical condition
at the hospital.
[tense music playing]
[Damian] I am the real Jaguar.
Your fake boss…
Tell him to give me back my men,
my money, my weapons!
-[gun fires]
-[Jaguar laughing]
[Diego] Auntie, we had no choice.
-Lily would've been discovered?
-When Arnaldo wakes up,
Lily's done for!
If she doesn't call, I'm going
with you to the Ardientes.
[Ivy] I didn't shoot Arnaldo!
-[men grunting]
-[electrocution]
Either you tell me the truth
or watch me unleash hell.
-Go ahead! Kill me!
-[drill whirring]